{"data":[{"question":"Our team has worked out the plan and now we must put it into ___.","a":"reality","b":"fact","c":"deed","d":"practice","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Put into practice: Carry out in action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Here's my car. Let's keep in ___.","a":"relation","b":"touch","c":"friendship","d":"connection","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Keep in touch: to maintain communications with someone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"We'll look into the case as soon as possible. Just have a little ___.","a":"time","b":"wait","c":"rest","d":"patience","answer":"4","explain":".","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"If by any chance somebody comes to see me, ask him\/her to leave a ___.","a":"letter","b":"message","c":"notice","d":"sentence","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Leave a message: write something and give to person you want to meet","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Something was wrong with___ motorcycle, but fortunately they know how to fix it.","a":"Ron and Kevin's","b":"Ron's and Kevin's","c":"Ron and Kevin","d":"Ron's and Kevin","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Motorcycle: singular- one motorcycle= Ron and Kevin's is correct","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"My family went to my ___ yesterday and had a good time.","a":"uncles","b":"uncles'","c":"uncle","d":"uncle's","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Uncle's = Uncle's family","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"I wonder whose car it is. \"It might be my ___.\"","a":"dear neighbor","b":"neighbor's","c":"neighbors","d":"neighbor","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Neighbor's = neighbor's car","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"___ will make a trip around the world during the coming vacation.","a":"The Newtons'","b":"The Newtons","c":"The Newton's","d":"The Newtones","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When a family name (a proper noun) is pluralized, we almost always simply add an \"s\" \n- The Newtons' = something of The Newtons","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"He is allowed ___to finish it.","a":"six days time","b":"six day's time","c":"six-days time","d":"six days' time","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Six days' time= time of six days = six-day's time","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The French people ___.","a":"are a great people","b":"is a great people","c":"are great peoples","d":"are great people","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n - The French peple: plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}